Guide to the Stanford University, School of Law, Faculty Meeting Minutes
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, School of Law, faculty meeting minutes
1917-1967
SC0770
Stanford University. School of Law.
1.5 Linear feet
This collection consists largely of minutes with some agenda, reports, and memoranda. Faculty minutes date from 1917-1967; committee records appear when they pertain to a faculty meeting and do not appear prior to 1950. Subjects covered include grading, schedules, special considerations taken during wartime, student petitions, classes offered, requirements for degrees, library matters, professional and national associations, appointments, scholarships, and fundraising. These copies were originally sent to the president's office; some were initialed by Ray L. Wilbur and a few have his handwritten comments.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
This collection consists largely of minutes with some agenda, reports, and memoranda. Faculty minutes date from 1917-1967; committee records appear when they pertain to a faculty meeting and do not appear prior to 1950. Subjects covered include grading, schedules, special considerations taken during wartime, student petitions, classes offered, requirements for degrees, library matters, professional and national associations, appointments, scholarships, and fundraising. These copies were originally sent to the president's office; some were initialed by Ray L. Wilbur and a few have his handwritten comments.
Access Terms
Stanford University. School of Law --Administration.; Stanford University. School of Law--Faculty.; Stanford University. School of Law.; Law schools--California.
Collection Contents
- Records
  - Meeting minutes, 1917-1923 Apr (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Meeting minutes, 1923 (Oct-1924 (May) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Meeting minutes, 1924 Sep-1927 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Meeting minutes, 1928-1931 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Meeting minutes, 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Meeting minutes, 1936-1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, 1941-1946 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Meeting minutes, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Meeting minutes, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Meeting minutes, 1949-1951 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Meeting minutes, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Meeting minutes, 1958-1959 May (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Meeting minutes, 1959 Sep-1960 Jan (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Meeting minutes, 1960 Feb-Dec (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, 1960 Sep-1961 July (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Meeting minutes, 1961 Jun-1962 May (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Meeting minutes, 1965-1966 Jun (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Meeting minutes, 1966 Sep-1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)